You
Trust me, this looks weird, but it works. Excuse me, sir. Won't this damage the machine?
Don't worry. Now
It's no big deal. It's mostly timing
Sir, thank you. You've really brightened our day. How did you get so good at this game?
Well, I've had time to perfect my technique. First, you move the claw above or over the edge of the chute.
Next, you start moving it around until it's got a nice spin on it.
Then release it at the height of its spin. This way the claw drops diagonally.
If you catch something, the claw drags it back to where you positioned it. So if it's right above the chute, it'll drop straight down
And you claim your price. It's all pretty straightforward. Like I said, it's mostly about timing and that takes some practice
Right now get excited. Remember you're playing a kid
Hugging it works too
It's cute. It's cute, isn't it?
Hey, I finally have an address for you. They're at 48 Tongli Lane apartment 607
Sir, thank you for all of your help today
No problem. So are these medicinal herbs?
My daughter's doctor prescribed them
What a coincidence. Seems like the creeper is also their neighbor
I've been wondering why my apartment smells like herbs all the time
Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't realize it was wafting over next door
It's fine
I mean, it's all for her, right? So kid, what's your name?
Don't you touch her!
I think we've officially found the brother we've been looking for
Zhang Xiaxia got an address 48 Tongli Lane, the Nanda district
Right, good work
Hey, Wang, are they still there? Don't let them leave
Then pull everything we have on Li Ulan. Thanks
Sorry about him. He can get a little overprotective, especially of his sister
No worries. It's natural for brothers to protect their sisters
Oh, thanks again for your help. That claw game was tough. I'm glad you showed up
Don't thank him
That guy's so sketchy. I bet his whole nice guy thing is an act. I hate people who do that
He's so angry. I wonder what happened to make him so hostile toward others
You shouldn't let people like him touch you, understand? And you should really learn to protect yourself
Don't laugh. I'm serious, okay? You know who wins? The strongest. If you're weak, people will hurt you
So yeah, you've got to learn to fight back and say no, right? Then you can beat those jerks up if they mess with you
Are all boys his age this dramatic or is he a special case?
Ask him who taught you that
How am I supposed to do that if I'm mute
Sign language ready
Take your finger raise it up wave it side to side
Now rotate that same finger in front of your mouth several times
Huh? Oh, I have this super cool new friend now. He told me about it
Oh
Here oh, you gotta do better. I can't be friends with a chicken
He didn't even care about getting in trouble or anything
Just jumped right in the fountain. It was the coolest thing I'd ever seen in my whole life
Oh
Since when was fountain diving cool? That's basic bad kid stuff
Speaking from experience
Haha, very funny
By the way, what was with your terrible signing just now? You forget what I taught you?
No sign I want to go home go
Point to yourself then nod
That was terrible
You're supposed to point at your chest make sense
Good now try again
Point and then nod your head
Why do you keep nodding your head all you need to do is point at it
What happened to pointing to my chest nothing you point to your chest and then at your head
That's what I did take it easy. It's not that hard first you point to your chest
Good next point to your head. Oh
No, that's wrong
Try again
I'm starting to think neither of you knows what you're doing
Hush now point to your head
No, you're still doing it wrong
I'm doing exactly what I was told to do
I'm doing it wrong
Here this part means I and this means want and
That was the sign for to return
Now make a triangle with your fingers then bring it up all the way here and that means home
Put it all together. It means I wanna go
Luke Wong got it
Hello? Are you still there?
Luke Wong
All right this time do it yourself
I didn't mean to say nod your head before but I should have said was point to yourself and then to your temple
Dude, why did you go dark all of a sudden?
I didn't
Seriously, is it possible for us to have a bad connection?
Hey, what's with that face?
Oh
How was work?
Fine
We were able to finish up before years end
Dianchen
Chishi dinner's ready
It looks like someone learned some new signs today
Huh? I haven't seen him before
When'd you get him?
She won it from a claw machine actually
We stopped by the store on the way back from the doctors
Wow, she won this by herself?
I thought all those machines were rigged
Oh
Well, I did have to help out a bit
And we got lucky
We won it on the last coin
Let's put him away while we eat dinner
We don't want to get him dirty
Come on, let's eat
Dianchen
Come and sit down please
Wow
I can't wait until all of this is in my stomach
Please remember that you're still a little kid
Don't eat like you
Come on, man
Time traveling is hard at work
And if I can at least get a full stomach out of it
Then I'm quitting
Here, meat will help you get big and strong
He's such a good brother
You're too skinny as is
Eat your food
Whatever
Excuse me, young man
Where did you learn to be so rude?
It's natural for boys his age to push back
It's like he grew into a teenager when we weren't looking
Kids grow up a lot faster these days
Hey, hey, dibs on the last two kills
These noobs think they can take the top killed?
As kill leader, I can't let that slide
All right, let's go
Eat this, you try hard
That's what you get
I forgot how nice this was
Eating with family
Since you're caught up, you gonna take a break from work?
Not anytime soon
The factory is looking to promote some people
It'd look bad if I took time off now
With as long as you've been an advanced employee
I think everyone would be disappointed if you didn't make deputy director this time
Deputy director is just a title
An empty one at that
Well, if your dad can't take a break then neither can you, Tianjin
You need to adjust that attitude if you want to do well in school
Or make friends, understand?
Hey, have we finally figured out what can't lose my good brother means yet?
Is he sick?
Is he going to be sick?
Honey, be honest
Did you buy a camera?
Uh, um, what? No, I haven't
Why ask?
Well, there's a camera sitting on the cabinet
A camera that I've never seen before today
Wait, you saw a camera?
Are you sure it wasn't something else?
Don't hold that with me
You think I didn't notice you trying to hide it?
Come on, let's eat, okay?
It's there
You hid it behind that toy hoping that I wouldn't see
I'm trying to be the better person here and give you the chance to explain yourself
But you chose to lie to me
What's happening right now?
Now, who gave this to you?
I bought it for Shishi and me
Bullshit! I know it was that teacher
Do you think people don't know what you've been doing with that man in our home?
Hey, busy day?
Yeah
Thankfully, it's over
Oh, by the way, do you want this pack of cigarettes?
Someone at work gave them to me and I didn't want to be rude, but as you know, I don't smoke
Thank you, but it wouldn't be a problem for me to accept them
No, please
They're wasted on me
All right, then
Hey, hold on
Man to man
You should probably have a talk with your wife
That teacher you mentioned
He came by today and I don't think he was here to talk about your kids
Is this a thank you for all the fun you had?
Is it?
You goddamn whore!
How many times did you cheat on me with him?
Don't you dare act surprised
You knew how I would react
You still lifted your skirt like a filthy bitch you are
No, I didn't
We talked about schools for Shishi
Mr. Cho only wants to help her
He's trying to get her into a special program
You think he actually cares about Shishi?
He doesn't care about either of our kids
There's only one thing men care about
You would know
It wouldn't help Shishi anyway
Even if we had the money
She doesn't need a program
She needs to learn how to be a good wife and mother
Or how not to be one
Hers can't stop batting her eyes at any man she happens to come across
See
Here's what I don't get
Why lie to me about Mr. Cho
If the whole neighborhood knows what you're doing
Why don't you just own up to it?
Now I can't trust you
Like this
You didn't win this
It was another gift from him, wasn't it?
You almost had me with that claw machine crap
Never again
No, please
I'm sorry
You! Take your sister and go to your room right now!
Don't come out!
Do not make me have to tell you twice!
Zhang Xiaoxi…
What did I say?!
Stop crying!
We're here because you kept pushing me!
Stop!
Do you think I like this?
I don't want to hurt you, but you forced my hand!
I'm giving this family everything!
I'm a good person!
I just wanted a little respect and you couldn't even do that yourself!
Kick them all down!
Do not let them crush them all!
This is it!
Let's show these chumps where the real gamers are!
Tastes my wrath!
Pathetic!
All these brats know how to do is talk!
What a bunch of posers!
Kneel scrub!
I am your god!
You asked for this!
Come on!
Let's go!
Damn you!
Slut!
Whore!
Please brother!
Do something!
You had enough?
Huh?
Are you gonna lie to me some more?
He didn't even care about getting in trouble or anything!
Just jumped right in the fountain!
It was the coolest thing I've ever seen in my whole life!
Here!
You gotta do better!
I can't be friends with a chicken!
Is this fun for you?!
Do you like ruining my reputation?!
Don't you dare!
Get back here!
Ah!
Gigi!
Now you beg for mercy?!
Sounds like a skill issue!
Hold up!
Someone's at my door!
Hello?
Huh?
I see!
So that's how it is!
All it takes is a few snacks and toys for you to call him dad!
Well, hasn't your mother embarrassed me enough?!
Stop that!
Now!
You hate me that much?!
Fine then!
You won't want me to be the bad guy!
I'm not gonna let you do that to me!
I'll kill us all first!
No, please!
If you need to blame someone, blame me!
Huh?
I know you don't mean that!
You're just trying to protect the kids!
It's too late!
What'd you find?
Bad news.
Liu Lan was murdered seven years ago.
What happened?
The report says she was found dead along with her husband, Li Fan.
Hold on.
Her husband's dead too?
Who's there?
Uh, just me.
So, I'm in 606.
Did you happen to see who was knocking on my door?
You're mistaken.
We didn't hear any knocking.
Uh, everything good?
We found a mouse.
Haven't got him yet.
Hammer's been giving me trouble.
It can't tell what it's hitting, so perhaps you should mind your own business.
Well, please keep it down, or I'll have to call the cops.
I told you his nice guy thing was just an act.
It's just one thing after another.
So what was that?
Did you seduce the neighbor too?
Is that why he wanted to play hero?
Is there no man he won't let have a turn with you?
I'm picking for help for divorce.
You can remarry.
No.
Why should you get what you want?
Huh?
Why you?
You make me a punchline!
I'll die before I let you take anything else from me!
Your house forія came to me!
Without Resì, I bet you can keep turning points!
There was nothing else from ruin place at school.
What's that?
What...
You're not talking about security for faults.
That's why I did.
Don't say security for us.
All right, you got me.
Can I at least know your name?
Sure.
It's Li Tenxie.